Hi everyone! Welcome to a new jumpsuit up video! It's time for two jumpsuits today
from a brand called Bonafide and the outfit I'm wearing right now is also
from this brand. I do love the leggings, I think the design is so cool and it fits
so good. So I hope that the jumpsuits are going to fit as well. A bit similar this one
with shiny parts and also a thicker jumpsuit with a corset like part in the middle. So
we'll see how they look and I hope you're going to enjoy this video.
First jumpsuit.
And I really love the look of it.
Reminds me a bit of the leggings from before with these parts here.
And this is also part mesh so slightly see through.
Or better breathing effect whatever because actually this is activewear.
It's an activewear brand from Russia and I see no one in German gyms wearing jumpsuits
for training.
But apparently I follow Bonafide on Instagram and they post a lot of hot girls in gyms wearing this kind of stuff for training and working out. Wow. This one is called Sex Suit Long.
And yeah, if you wear it for sports or something else like the name indicates, it's up to you.
And I can already hear the YouTube police coming because of the name.
Yeah, I mean it also has this thong kind of cut here.
And it's overall very figure-hugging and tight.
I'm wearing size extra small.
I think I would go up a size next time because it's slightly too short you can see it here
It pulls the waistband here up
So you can see it's a bit too short. Although the leggings are extra small. They were fine, but I think for an overall
size S would be
better
Otherwise, I really like the look
so I
Think it's some better some kind of lazy wear. I don't know. I
I would not wear it in a gym. Not really. Would you?
This is really really stylish with the different kinds of fabric and also with the heels I paired it with.
But I have a second one. So we'll move on to the next one.
We'll be right back.
second jumpsuit and it's so comfortable because it's so cozy it has like this
winter fabric which is thicker and yeah more cuddly so I really feel warm and
comfortable and snuggly but I mean of course the other one looks more intricate
and this is like a bit plain compared to the first one although we have different
features like the stripes here and here and this corset like part in the middle
so yeah it's black and it is not as exciting as the other one but it's still
cool and it like I said it's really cozy so plus point for that and also it fits
better in size extra small it's longer somehow so it's more comfortable for me
at least and I paired it with some flat platform sneaker for a more supportive
look I really like this signature stitching stripe here they both have it
and it disappears when I close the catsuit. Wow now it's really black. So I
think it adds a bit more contrast also. I noticed that the zipper has a really
weird shape and at the beginning I was like what is that until I realized that
it's supposed to be a booty. Yeah, sportswear. I prefer it like this. I think each of them
has their plus points and also still love the first leggings I showed you. So yeah,
I'm done here for today and I hope you're going to have a nice day and check out my
patreon because I have a lot of bonus content there also leave comment thumbs
up subscribe to my channel all that stuff if you want to support me see you
around bye